{
    "subject": "resource/Edgar_Rice_Burroughs",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/H._Rider_Haggard",
    "human_readable": "Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by H. Rider Haggard.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9814261198043823,
            "question": "Did Edgar Rice Burroughs directly acknowledge H. Rider Haggard's influence on his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9805890917778015,
            "question": "Can you name a specific work by H. Rider Haggard that might have influenced Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9631856083869934,
            "question": "Who influenced Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8532706499099731,
            "question": "What genre did both Edgar Rice Burroughs and H. Rider Haggard write in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7780542969703674,
            "question": "Are there any similarities in the works of Edgar Rice Burroughs and H. Rider Haggard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7190727591514587,
            "question": "Did Edgar Rice Burroughs cite any literary influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.677575945854187,
            "question": "What was H. Rider Haggard known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48960259556770325,
            "question": "How did H. Rider Haggard's writing impact popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.016695471480488777,
            "question": "What were some of the popular themes explored by both authors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.015709377825260162,
            "question": "How did the literary landscape of the time period affect both authors?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by H. Rider Haggard.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7896_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the popular themes explored by both authors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7896_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did H. Rider Haggard's writing impact popular culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7896_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was H. Rider Haggard known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7896_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7896_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain evidence of Edgar Rice Burroughs' acquaintance with and admiration for H. Rider Haggard's work, as well as mentions of Burroughs being influenced by Haggard in certain aspects of his writing."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that supports the statement \"Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by H. Rider Haggard.\" Specifically, the texts mention that Robert W. Fenton's biography suggests Burroughs was indeed influenced by Haggard, particularly by his novel \"She,\" and that Burroughs' 1931 novel, \"Tarzan Triumphant,\" is a direct imitation in certain episodes, which further supports this influence."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}